Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory6 Mss.B.B61.inventory06
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents H
  - Hunt, George (Box 44-45)
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 5; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1916 May 7; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1916 June 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 July 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 July 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 May 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 June 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 June 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 June 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 July 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 July 22; bill
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept. 25; receipt
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept. 28; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec. 11; receipt
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Jan. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Feb. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Feb. 12; receipt
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 10; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 27; receipt
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 28; receipt
    - To Boas, 1919 May 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 July 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 5; receipt
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 14; receipt
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 1; receipt
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 30; receipt
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 May 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 8; receipt
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 12; #30; 1p.
      Contains the image Ma'mo'que'le'la
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 4; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Apr. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 July 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 7; receipt
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 5; bill
    - To Boas, 1923 June 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Sept. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 24; receipt
    - To Boas, 1924 May 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 June 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec.; bill
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 12; receipt
    - To Boas, 1925 May 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 10; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 May 14; receipt
    - To Boas, 1926 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 June 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 26; receipt
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 16; receipt
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 20; receipt
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 28; receipt
    - To Boas, 1927 May 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 14; receipt
    - To Boas, 1927 June 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 June 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 22; receipt
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 16; receipt
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 29; receipt
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Aug. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Sept. 25; invoice
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 17; receipt
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 29; receipt
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 2; receipt
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 17; receipt
    - To Boas, 1929 July 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 1; receipt
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 26
    - (See Cadwallader, Mr. and Mrs. W.I.), 1932 Apr. 14
    - (Receipt attached), 1932 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - (See letter from Boas, F. to Hunt, Johnnie dated 10-5-33), 1933 June 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, n.d.
    - (Attached to letter dated May 5, 1931 from Boas, F. to Hunt, George), n.d.
    - (Receipt attached to letter from Boas, F. July 13, 1931), n.d.; 1p.
    - (Attached to letter to Hunt of 1-16-33)
    - G. Hunt -- from H.A. Andrews, 1901 Aug. 29
    - G. Hunt -- from H.A. Andrews, 1901 Sept. 21
    - G. Hunt -- from H.A. Andrews, 1911 Feb. 11
    - G. Hunt -- to H.A. Andrews, 1911 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - G. Hunt -- to Keith W. Bryan, 1931 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - G. Hunt -- to R.W. Bryan, 1929 July 14; 1p.
    - G. Hunt -- to Columbia University, 1924 July 2; 1p.
    - G. Hunt -- to Columbia University, 1930 June 27; 1p.
    - G. Hunt -- to Columbia University, 1931 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - G. Hunt -- from G.F. Newcombe, 1906 July 5
    - G. Hunt -- from U.S. Bureau of American Ethnology, 1918 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - Hunt, George
      - Jesup North Pacific Expedition. -- Miscellaneous documents, 1900-1932
    - (See Hunt, George, 1900-1901)
  - Hunt, H. T. (Box 45)
    9/94 See also Box after B/861 p labelled Newsclippings, printed matter, etc.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - (Enc: list of members), 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
  - Hunt, Johnnie (Box 45)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 14; 1p.
  - Hunt, W.M.? (Box 45)
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 5; 1p.
  - Hunter, Arthur (Box 45)
    - A. Hunter -- to Frida Reiche, 1929 July 1; 1p.
    - (On reverse side: Hunter, A. to Reiche, F., Nov. 6, 1929)
    - A. Hunter -- to F. Reiche, 1929 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - (Copy enc. with Reiche, F., Oct. 27, 1929)
  - Hunter, A.B. (Box 45)
    - From Boas, 1903 July 18; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 May 9; 2p.
  - Hunter, A.L.P. (Box 45)
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 1; 1p.
  - Hunter, W.S. (Box 45)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 14; 1p.
  - Hunter College of New York (Box 45)
    See Kayser, Carl F.
  - Huntington,? (Box 45)
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept. 22; 1p.
  - Huntington, Archer M. (Box 45)
    - From Boas, 1903 May 8; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1905 June 1
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 17
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 28
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 14; 5p.
    - From Boas, 1909 June 21
    - From Boas, 1909 June 23
    - From Boas, 1909 June 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 25
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 6
    - (See Boas, F. to Dixon, R.B. Jan. 6, 1911), 1911 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 25
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1911 Feb. 28
    - (See Boas, F. to ChC!vez, E.A. Feb. 28, 1911), 1911 Mar. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 21
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 10
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 May 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 May 18
    - From Boas, 1911 June 2
    - From Boas, 1911 June 6
    - From Boas, 1911 June 9
    - From Boas, 1911 June 17; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Dec.; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 17
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 July 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1915 May 26
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 10; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 10
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 June 6
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1909 May 19 and June 24
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1911 May 17
    - To Boas, 1911 May 27
    - To Boas, 1911 June 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1915 May 21
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 13
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - A.M. Huntington -- from International school of American archaeology and ethnology. Secretary, 1911 Jan. 6
    - A.M. Huntington -- to E.C. Parsons, 1920 June 1; 2p.
    - (Enc: Parsons, E.C. to Boas, Aug. 7, 1920)
    - A.M. Huntington -- from E.C. Parsons, 1917 June 11
    - A.M. Huntington -- from E.C. Parsons, 1925
  - Huntington, Ellsworth (Box 45)
    - 1913 Feb. 24 and Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 29; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 4; telegram
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 7; 1p.
  - Huntington, George S. (Box 45)
    - To Boas, 1898 May 2; 1p.
  - Hunziker (Box 45)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept. 22; 1p.
  - Huot, Martha Lee (Box 45)
    - M.L. Huot -- to American Council of Learned Societies, 1941 May 14; 1p.
  - Hupfel, J.C.G. (Box 45)
    - To Boas, E.L., 1904 June 21; 1p.
  - Hurd, H.M. (Box 45)
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 9
  - Hurdman, F.H. (Box 45)
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 28; 1p.
  - Hurlburt, George C. (Box 45)
    - To Boas, 1887 Aug. 6
    - To Boas, 1887 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1887 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 2
  - Hurlburt, I. (Box 45)
    - From Boas
    - See margin of Scholefield, E.P. to Teit, J.A., Apr. 24, 1907.
  - Hurlburt, T. (Box 45)
    - See margin, Scholefield, E.P. to Teit, J.A., Apr. 24, 1907.
  - Hurley, J. (Box 45)
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 4; 2p.
  - Hurrey (Box 45)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 31; 1p.
  - Hurst, C.B. (Box 45)
    - C.B. Hurst -- to Keppel, 1906 Aug. 17
  - Hurst, F. (Box 45)
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 2; 1p.
  - Hurst, S.S. (Box 45)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 11; 1p.
  - Hurston, Zora N. (Box 45)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1927 June 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - Z.N. Hurston -- to O. Klineberg, 1929 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - Z.N. Hurston -- from Julius Rosenwald Fund, 1934 Dec. 19
  - Hurwitz, Henry (Box 46)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 19; 1p.
  - Husband, W.W. (Box 46)
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1908 June 9
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 12
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 24; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 19
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 21
    - From Boas, 1909 May 5
    - From Boas, 1909 May 24
    - From Boas, 1909 May 27
    - From Boas, 1909 June 1
    - From Boas, 1909 June 12
    - From Boas, 1909 July 2
    - From Boas, 1909 July 3
    - From Boas, 1909 Aug. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 9
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 26
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 3
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 20
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 May 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 May 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 May 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 July 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 July 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 July 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 June 6
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 12; telegram
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 13; telegram
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 15; telegram
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 19; telegram
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1909 May 26
    - To Boas, 1909 May 28
    - To Boas, 1909 June 2
    - To Boas, 1909 June 12
    - To Boas, 1909 June 14
    - To Boas, 1909 July 6
    - To Boas, 1909 July 8
    - To Boas, 1909 July 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept. 29; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 23; telegram
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 12; telegram
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 26; telegram
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 May 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 June 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 June 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Sept. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 10; telegram
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 19; telegram
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 22; telegram
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 2; telegram
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - (Enc: Blank from Immigration service), 1929 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 5; 2p.
    - W.W. Husband -- to H.A. Andrews, 1911 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - W.W. Husband -- to H.A. Andrews, 1911 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - W.W. Husband -- to H.A. Andrews, 1911 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - W.W. Husband -- to H.A. Andrews, 1911 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - W.W. Husband -- from H.A. Andrews, 1911 Jan. 10
    - W.W. Husband -- from H.A. Andrews, 1911 Jan. 14
    - W.W. Husband -- from H.A. Andrews, 1911 Jan. 16
    - W.W. Husband -- from H.A. Andrews, 1911 Jan. 21
    - W.W. Husband -- from H.A. Andrews, 1911 Jan. 21
  - Husemann, Frida (Hahn) (Box 46)
    See Hahn, Frida K.
  - Huser? E.J. (Box 46)
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 23; 1p.
  - Huss, B. (Box 46)
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 12; 1p.
  - Hutchins, Robert M. (Box 46)
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec.; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 May 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 3; telegram
  - Huth, George (Box 46)
    - To Boas, 1903 Mar. 8; 7p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Aug. 20; 1p.
  - Huttman, M.A. (Box 46)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 25; 2p.
  - Huxley, Henry M. (Box 46)
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 11; 1p.
  - Hyatt, Harry M. (Box 46)
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 26; 1p.
  - Hyde, B. Talbot B. (Box 46)
    - From Boas, 1900 June 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1905 May 25
    - From Boas, 1905 May 27
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1908 May 23
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 6